A Guide to the Records of Jamestown 2007, 1986-2009
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of Jamestown 2007, 1986-2009
The Library of Virginia
44449
79 cubic feet
Jamestown 2007
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation on 20 August 2009.
Historical Information
In 1996, the General Assembly amended article 23-292 of the Code of Virginia, to establish the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation as the Commonwealth's authorized agency to "to perform the following actions directly related to the planning, coordination and implementation of the celebration of the 400th anniversary of the founding of Jamestown in 1607. Jamestown 2007 is a sub-agency of the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (JYF) created in 1997 to plan and implement commemorative events marking the 400th anniversary of the founding of Jamestown, the first permanent English settlement in the Americas. From 1997 through 2004, the agency focused on developing the structure of the commemoration including recruiting volunteer board and committee leadership, conceptualizing the signature events, creating strategies to achieve the goals of the commemoration, forging partnerships with appropriate public and private organizations, seeking corporate sponsorships and building a staffing plan. By the beginning of 2005 a new phase of the commemoration work began with the movement from planning to implementation. Prosody Creative Services was retained through Jamestown 2007's private affiliate to produce the Godspeed Promotional Sail, the Yorktown 225th Anniversary, the National Teach-In and Anniversary Weekend. Other partnerships and consultants have been or are being selected to perform key roles in implementing the other signature events.
Scope and Content
The Records of Jamestown 2007 are arranged in eight series. Series have been designated for History Files - Agency; Public Relations - Historically Significant; Recordings - Audio/Visual - Historically Significant; Project Documentation Files - Historically Significant; Planning Files - Administrative - Historically Significant; Special Interest Items; Correspondence/Subject Files - Agency Heads; and Correspondence/Subject Files - Other Officials - Historically Significant.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. History Files - Agency, 1986-2008
Series II. Public Relations - Historically Significant, 2003-2008
Series III. Recordings - Audio/Visual - Historically Significant, 2006-2007
Series IV. Project Documentation Files - Historically Significant, 2000-2008
Series V. Planning Files - Administrative - Historically Significant, 2001-2007
Series VI. Special Interest Items, 2001-2009
Series VII. Correspondence/Subject Files - Agency Heads, 1997-2007
Series VIII. Correspondence/Subject Files - Other Officials - Historically Significant, 1996-2007
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Electronic records have also been transferred with these records.
Contents List
- Series I: History Files - Agency, 1986-2008., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 1-18)
  Series I: History Files contains minutes, reports, proposals, and other sundry items documenting the work of various committees including the Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee, Joint Steering Committee, Executive Committee, Creative Advisory Committee, Program & Events Subcommittee, Marketing & Finance Subcommittee, Logistics Subcommittee, Management Subcommittee, and the Historic Triangle Host Committee. In addition, the Celebration 2007 Committee documents early planning for the 400th anniversary.
  - Celebration 2007 - Critical Path, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Celebration 2007 - Critical Path - Beyond the Concept, 2001. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Celebration 2007 - Early Planning, 1986-1997. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Celebration 2007 - Early Planning, 1997-1998. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Celebration 2007 - Early Planning, 1999. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Celebration 2007 - Roundtable, 1998 Jan.-June. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Celebration 2007 - Roundtable, 1998 July-Oct.. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Celebration 2007 - Roundtable, 1999 Mar.-Aug.. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Celebration 2007 - Roundtable, 1999 Sept.-Dec.. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Celebration 2007 - Strategic Planning Retreat, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Creative Advisory Committee Minutes, 2004-2007. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Creative Advisory Committee Minutes, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Inclusion - African American, 1999-2003. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Inclusion - African American - African-American Advisory Council, undated. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Inclusion - African American Forum, 2002-2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Inclusion - African American - - NAACP Roundtable, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cultural Inclusion - Virginia Indians, 1998-2007. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Inclusion - Virginia Indians - News Clips, 1999-2007. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Cultural Inclusion - Virginia Indians - VIAC, 2005-2006. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Inclusion - Virginia Indians - Visiting Specialists, 2003-2005. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 2000-2001. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 2002-2004. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 2005-2007. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Art Grants, 1999. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Community Activities Task Force Meeting Notes, undated. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Community Conservation Program and Training, undated. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Community Guest Orientation, undated. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Customer Service Standards, undated. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Final Volunteer Report, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Guest Orientation, undated. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Marketing, Promotion, and Public Information, undated. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Meeting Notes, 2004-2005. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Pamphlets, undated. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Prepare, Care, Share, undated. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Resource Notebook, undated. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Training Modules, undated. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Volunteer Handbook, undated. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Website Proposal, undated. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Historic Triangle Host Committee - Working Groups, 2001-2004. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Joint Fundraising - JYF, Jamestown 2007, NPS, & APVA, 2002-2005. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Joint Steering Committee Minutes, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Joint Steering Committee Minutes, 1999. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joint Ticketing - JYF, NPS/APVA, 2001-2005. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Leadership Committee Minutes, 1998-2002. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local (Primary) Partners - National Park (NPS) and APVA, 1998-2005. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Logistics Committee Comprehensive Transportation Plan, 2003. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Logistics Committee Minutes, 1998-2000. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Logistics Committee - Transportation - Correspondence, 1998-2007. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Logistics Committee - Transportation - Studies, 1998-2000. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Logistics Committee - Working Groups, 1998-2000. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Logo - Athletic Patch, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Logo - Design - Just Partners, 2001. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Logo - Design - Lab - RFP, Presentations, 1998-2005. (Box 18, Folder 4a)
  - Logo - Early Planning, 1995-2004. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Logo - Logo Use and Agreements, 1998-2005. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Logo - Merchandising - Design Lab - Product Catalog & Royalties, 2005-2007. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Logo - Merchandising - Design Lab - Proposal, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Management Subcommittee Weekly Reports, 2004-2005. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Management Subcommittee Weekly Reports, 2006-2007. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Communications Plan, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Marketing & Finance Subcommittee - "Jamestown: Investing in an American Legacy", undated. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Marketing & Finance Subcommittee Minutes, 1997-2002. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Firms - Chumara - Campaign Analysis, 2004-2007. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Firms - KD Paine - Awareness Audit, 2007-2008. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Marketing - Public Relations Firms - Ruder Finn - Budget, Updates, undated. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marketing - Public Relations Firms - Ruder Finn - Proposal, Initial Meet, 2005-2008. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marketing - Public Relations Firms - Siddall - Godspeed Sail, 2005-2006. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Marketing - VTC - Marketing Plan, The New World Campaign, 2004-2008. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marketing - Williamsburg Area Convention and Visitor, The Advertiser, 2003-2004. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Media Coverage - CD - WHRO - Building an American Celebration, 1999-2001. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Media Coverage - Film - The New World Premiere, 2005. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Media Coverage - Presentation to American Press Association, undated. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Media Coverage - Print - Clipping Service - Newswatch, 2003. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Media Coverage - Print - Inserts, Posters, undated. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Media Coverage - Print - Official Publication - "The Journey That Changed the World," 2007. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Media Coverage - Print - Press Releases, 1997-2007. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Media Coverage - Print - Tommy Norment Op Ed, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Media Coverage - Research on Virginia Celebrities, 2003-2004. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - One Jamestown, 1999-2000. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - One Jamestown, 2001. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - One Jamestown - Training and Route 359, 2001. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Op Sail, 1998-2000. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Primary Partner Colonial Williamsburg, 1998-2004. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Correspondence, 1998-2003. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Minutes, 1998-2001. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Minutes, 2002-2003. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Proposals, 1999. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Vision Statements, 1999. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Working Groups, 1997-2000. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Program and Events Subcommittee Working Groups, 2000-2004. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sponsorships - Consultant - Velocity, 2002-2006. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sponsorships - Consultant - Velocity - Presentations, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Sponsorships - Declined, 1999. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Sponsorships - Declined, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Sponsorships - Declined, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Sponsorships - Declined, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Sponsorships - Early Planning, 2003-2004. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Sponsorships - Media - The History Channel, 2001-2006. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Sponsorships - Sponsorship Kits, undated. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Steering Committee - Elizabeth Bickford, 1999. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee - History, 1996-2002. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee - History Compilation, 1996-2003. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 1996-1997. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 1998-1999. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 2000-2001. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 2002-2004. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee Minutes, 2005-2007. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series II: Public Relations - Historicaly Significant, 2003-2008., Extent: 39 boxes. (Box 19-57)
  Series II: Public Relations is the largest series in the collection. This series contains binders of news clippings documenting various articles related to Jamestown and the 400th anniversary celebration between July 2003 through January 2008, especially in May 2007.
  - News Clippings, 2003 July-2004. (Box 19)
  - News Clippings, 2004 July-2005 March. (Box 20)
  - News Clippings, 2005 April-August. (Box 21)
  - News Clippings, 2005 September-December. (Box 22)
  - News Clippings, 2006 January-March. (Box 23)
  - News Clippings, 2006 April-May. (Box 24)
  - News Clippings, 2006 June-July. (Box 25)
  - News Clippings, 2006 August. (Box 26)
  - News Clippings, 2006 September. (Box 27)
  - News Clippings, 2006 October. (Box 28)
  - News Clippings, 2006 November 1-20. (Box 29)
  - News Clippings, 2006 November 10-15, 21-30. (Box 30)
  - News Clippings, 2006 December. (Box 31)
  - News Clippings, 2007 January 1-16. (Box 32)
  - News Clippings, 2007 January-March. (Box 33)
  - News Clippings, 2007 February. (Box 34)
  - News Clippings, 2007 March. (Box 34)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April. (Box 35)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April 1-8. (Box 36)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April 9-21. (Box 37)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April 22-26. (Box 38)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April 27-29. (Box 39)
  - News Clippings, 2007 April 29-30. (Box 40)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 1-3. (Box 41)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 3-4. (Box 42)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 4-5. (Box 43)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 5. (Box 44)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 6-8. (Box 45)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 9-11. (Box 46)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 12-13. (Box 47)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 14. (Box 48)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 15-17. (Box 55)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 18-23. (Box 56)
  - News Clippings, 2007 May 24-31. (Box 57-1)
  - News Clippings, 2007 June 1-24. (Box 49)
  - News Clippings, 2007 July. (Box 50)
  - News Clippings, 2007 August. (Box 51)
  - News Clippings, 2007 September. (Box 52)
  - News Clippings, 2007 October-November. (Box 53)
  - News Clippings, 2007 December-2008 January. (Box 54)
- Series III: Recordings - Audio/Visual - Historically Significant, 2006-2007., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 57-58)
  Series III: Recordings contains compact discs, videotapes, and other video recording formats documenting several anniversary events including the Godspeed Sail, Anniversary Weekend, Intertribal Festival, Smithsonian FolkLife Fest, Yorktown 225th Anniversary, and others.
  - 2007 Comm. Session (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - 2007 Kick-Off Photos (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - AAF PowerPoint (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - African Imprint Day Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Airport Display Panels (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - An American Symphony (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th - President Bush, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th Anniversary (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th Anniversary - Jamestown B-Roll (Betacam), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - America's 400th - Chorus, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th Day 1 - Stamp, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th Day 2 - Boats, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th Day 3 - President Bush, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th - Jay Paul (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th - Jay Paul (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th - Jay Paul after President (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's 400th - President Bush, etc. (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's Anniversary Garden (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America's Anniversary Presentation (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - America Today: 400 Years Strong (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Amy Ritchie Photo (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anne Dale Photo (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Voices (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Voices Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Weekend (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Weekend - Exhibitors Banner (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Weekend Godspeed Sail - Complete (DVCPro), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Anniversary Weekend Godspeed Sail - Highlights (DVCPro), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Anniversary Weekend - Jamestown Island (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Anniversary Weekend Settlement Interpreters (Betacam), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Anniversary Week Stamp Ceremony (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - APVA - Aerials, 2006 July (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Baa Bah Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Ba-Baah and the Windigo (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Black Expo (4 discs) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - British Delegation Images, 2006 (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - British Embassy (Betacam), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - British Embassy - Full Presentation (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - British Embassy Program (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - British Events (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Busch Gardens, 2007. (Box 58)
  - Center for Youth Summit Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Certificate of Appreciation (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Coming Home to Virginia (2 video clips) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Commemorative Coin Unveiling (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Community Brochure (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Community Conversation (CD), 2005. (Box 58)
  - Community Conversation - Bruton Heights (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Conversation Maps by Area (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Meeting - Legislative Reception (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Program - Certificate of Appreciation (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Program Kickoff Richmond (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Program Kickoff (CD), 2003. (Box 58)
  - Community Program Kickoff (VHS), 2003. (Box 57-2)
  - Community Program - Virginia 2007 (VHS), 2007. (Box 57-2)
  - Community Programs 2007 - Video/Web Ready (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Community Programs - VHS/CG Graphics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Bill Richmond (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Bill Richmond (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Charles - Pulaski County (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Diane - Smithfield/Sergie - Staunton (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Jim Ryan - Petersburg (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video - Mary - Prince William County (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Community Video Clips (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Compilation: Godspeed, SDO, PSA (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Cultural Community Conversation (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Friday (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed Arrives from Jamestown (Beta/VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Construction (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed - Under Sail, Interpreters (DVCPro), undated. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed - Under Sail, Interpreters (DVCPro), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Alexandria - Boat Tour (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Alexandria - Ship Landing (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Baltimore - Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Baltimore - Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Boston - Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Boston - Ship Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Commissioning (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Commissioning (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Newport - Ship Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - New York - Ship Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - New York - Ship Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Newsclips (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail - Philadelphia - Ship Arrival (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Godspeed Sail Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed Sail Pics - Alexandria (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed Sail Pics - New York (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Godspeed Sail - Yorktown (Mini DV), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Governor's Conference on American Indians (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Governor Warner with Native Americans (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Hampton Pow Wow (DVD), undated. (Box 58)
  - History Channel - History Day (VHS), 2001. (Box 57-2)
  - Images (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Images (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Images for Film (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Indians in England (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival Banner (CD), 2007. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival - Jay Paul (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival - Jay Paul (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival - Pics by Staff (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival - Pics by Staff (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Intertribal Festival - Pics by Staff (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 1957 - Michael May (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 1957 - Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 2007 - America's 400th Anniversary - CBS Special (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 2007 Brochure (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 2007 Celebration (VHS), 2003. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown 2007 in England (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown 2007 - Governor Warner Interview (Beta), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown 2007 Group Staff (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 2007 Individual & Group Staff Photos (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown 2007 - Virginia Indians - British Trip (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown Celebration (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Celebration (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Community Program Kick-Off (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Live! Sailing on Godspeed (DVCPro), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Live! Sailing on Godspeed (DVCPro), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Live! Tapes (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown - NASA Benefits of Working Together (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Jamestown News Clips (Beta 6), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown News Clips (Beta 6), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown Raw Footage (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Jamestown's PSA (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Journey Up the James Photos (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - JYF - Jamestown: The Beginning (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Kaine PSA Participate, Plant, Promote (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Kaine PSA Participate, Plant, Promote (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Life Performances (2 copies - 18 discs each) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - NASA - Landscape Archaeology - Hidden Treasures (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - National Geographic for Kids (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Naval Museum - 1907 Jamestown Postcards (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Negro Building Poster (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - New World Premiere Photos (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - New World Trailer (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Perspective PBS - Zeidler/Richardson (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Prosody B-Roll (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Prosody - Signature Events (10 discs) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Queen's Gift (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Reconciliation Statue, 2007. (Box 58)
  - Remembering Jamestown: Songs of Commemoration (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Richmond Region 400th (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Ross Richardson Photo, 2003 (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Signature Events (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Signature Events Highlights (video) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Smithsonian FolkLife Fest, 2007 (CD) - Miscellaneous, undated. (Box 58)
  - Smithsonian FolkLife Fest, 2007 (CD) - Miscellaneous, undated. (Box 58)
  - Smithsonian FolkLife Fest, 2007 - Virginia Indian Performance (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Sponsorship Corporate (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Sponsorship Kit (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Sponsorship Sales (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Sponsorship Sales (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - State of the Black Union (2 discs) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Steering Committee Interviews (Beta/VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Steering Committee Interviews (Beta/VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Steering Committee Interviews (Beta/VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Susan Constant - Under Sail (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Tavis Smiley (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)